We are wasting time.
Don't forget, Joey.
Blood is thicker than water.
What do you mean?
Andrew is related to Berdugo?
I always stand on
the side of truth,
even if my enemy is family.
This is what we need.
Because Tomas Limjoco
is the real Berdugo.
We're going to the rest house
to visit mommy.
I'll go with you guys.
This isn't true, Andrew.
This isn't true.
I'm sorry, Yvette,
but we don't have time.
We need to act now.
Tomas went with them.
Andrew, you go in first.
Secure your family.
Joey, you'll accompany them.
And you, Jin Ho, come with us.
You'll identify
if Tomas is Berdugo.
Where is Yvette? Where?
They're inside,
but Sir Tomas has a gun!
[GUNS FIRING]
Dad...
[OBB]
[MULTIPLE GUNFIRE]
Something might have happened
to dad.
I'll call you later, Peter!
Joey, wait...
[PHONE BEEPING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Major, are you okay?
Thank you.
[GUNS FIRING]
My hunch was right.
He figured out our plan, Major.
All units, we need backup!
I repeat, we need backup!
[GUNS FIRING]
Tomas Limjoco!
Surrender now!
We know your true identity!
Tomas!
We know you're Berdugo!
Go ahead and try!
We'll kill all
the hostages here!
The rest of you, stay here.
You two, follow me.
Yes, Sir! Let's go!
[GUNS FIRING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Hello, Dad?
What's happening? Are you okay?
Joey, we've been discovered.
Don't leave that spot,
it's dangerous.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PEOPLE CRYING]
Dad, why are you doing this
to us?
Daddy!
Take the children
to the other room.
[KISSES BAWLING]
What are you doing!
[CLAMORING]
Tomas! Don't!
Don't! Tomas!
No! No!
Tomas, what are you doing?
- Tomas!
- Tomas, stop!
Don't drag your family
into your viciousness!
What's wrong with you?
[SLAPS]
Tomas!
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Tomas, don't!
Tomas, please.
How dare you betray me?
You think I wouldn't sense it?
Hon, we're here.
Who were you talking to?
It's Andrew.
I told him to come here
so we can be together.
Go out to grandmother's garden,
okay?
But didn't you say
we shouldn't go out, Mommy?
You could, just for today.
It's okay.
Isn't it hot outside?
It's good for mommy too...
so she can breathe fresh air.
Ma'am, your basket is ready.
- It's in the garden.
- Why is that?
Because you always go straight
there when you come here.
Maybe next time, I want to spend
time with them, Nanny.
Sorry, here.
Mom, you keep dropping it!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Nestor!
Secure the gate and perimeter.
Tell the others.
Close the house!
Get them.
- Why?
- No one gets out!
- What? Why?
- What does this mean?
[CLAMORING]
What does this mean?
Did the police follow us?
No! What are you saying?
Boss, Tony texted.
There are police
in the vicinity!
You animal!
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
You betrayed me, Tomas!
Living a double life?
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
Leading a syndicate?
Everything about you is a lie!
Do you really want
to go against me?
[PHONE CHIMES]
Tell the others.
- [GUNS FIRING IN DISTANCE]
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[JOEY GRUNTING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Major, my family
is in danger inside.
You know what Tomas
can do to them!
[GUNS FIRING IN THE DISTANCE]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BULLETS PLINKING]
[PHONE RINGING]
Yvette!
Brother-in-law...
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
You animal!
What did you do to my family?
Release them!
They're my family too,
remember, Andrew.
[MAIDS SOBBING]
[SHRIEKING]
[GUN FIRING]
I won't hurt them...
for now.
So, tell Major Delgado...
to leave.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
If not, someone will die
here again.
Tomas, this won't help
your situation!
Surrender now!
Don't make it harder
for yourself!
I built my empire for decades,
Major.
I invested sweat and blood
in this business.
From small deals,
to life-threatening
transactions.
But the way you're talking,
it's like you're asking me
to close a small store.
That's the problem with the dead
who came back...
a screw is missing in the brain.
This is what should happen.
First, you will all leave
the compound.
Second, I will only talk to you.
If I hear even a hint
of noise...
or if anyone disobeys...
someone will die in here.
And last condition,
I need a vehicle...
with two fully-loaded long arms.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Hey!
Where are you going?
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
Put that down!
Are you crazy, Tomas?
We won't give you weapons!
No!
Major...
I can't be at a disadvantage.
You already cornered me here.
If you don't give me my demands,
no one will get out of here.
[GRUNTS]
[THUDS]
[CLACKS]
Come here!
- [THUDDING]
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [THUDS]
- [GOON GROANS]
- [THUDDING]
- [GROANING]
[CRASHES AND RATTLES]
[GUNS FIRING IN DISTANCE]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
You already know
you're at a disadvantage!
Why don't you surrender?
What, Tomas?
Don't involve others!
Stop your cruelty!
- [GUN FIRING]
- [CROWD SHRIEKING]
Mom!
[BAWLING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
You're an animal, Berdugo!
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
[MAIDS SOBBING]
Relax, Brother-in-law.
Your family is still alive.
However, no one will take care
of your mother anymore.
See?
I kept my end of the deal.
If anyone makes noise,
someone dies.
Now, it's your turn...
to do what I asked.
And I promise...
no noise, no one dies.
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
All right, Tomas,
I'll grant your request,
but on one condition.
You won't kill
any of your hostages.
You don't make the conditions,
Major.
But fine, I'll allow it.
But you only have 10 minutes.
When 10 minutes are up
and I don't get what I asked,
someone dies again here.
10 minutes, one life.
Tomas! They're your family...
[PHONE BEEPING]
[SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOBBING]
Please...
What?
Is this the first time
you've seen me like this?
That I'm different
from how you knew me?
Say it, it's okay.
I regret marrying a demon!
Well, you know what they say.
When you marry evil,
you become part of it.
You're not so innocent, Yvette.
You benefitted from me too.
You got your charity works
from my business.
I wouldn't have accepted it
if I knew it came
from evil deeds, Tomas!
No!
[PHONE RINGING]
[SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING]
They took the bait.
Get ready for extraction.
What's that?
You made a deal with the police,
but you have another plan?
That's the problem with Delgado.
He is gullible.
This is my home court,
so I decide who lives,
who dies,
and who escapes.
Now...
shut up or else I won't bring
the children back here!
Good choice.
[SINISTER MUSIC CONTINUES]
When you're done,
bring the children back here.
If Berdugo agrees,
we can execute plan A.
The vehicle is on its way,
Major.
Good.
Our priority is...
to keep Berdugo away
from his hostages.
Major, I don't think
he'll keep his word.
This is the only way
to save your family.
We need to take the risk.
All units, move out!
[INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Let's go!
[INTENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
My grandchildren!
[CLAMORING]
Are you okay? Kisses?
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE BUZZING]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Joey?
Hello, Jin Ho?
Do not tell anyone that I'm
the one you're talking to.
Okay, I'm listening.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Jin Ho!
Joey!
They are inside.
We can't get them
all out at once
without being noticed.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE KEYS CLICKING]
[PHONE CHIMES]
Cruz, stay alert.
Watch out for the vehicle.
[PHONE BUZZES]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Major, I think it's time
we execute plan B.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Here, I already reset the modem
while the LAN cables
were on the second port.
Then?
Ah, there, it's green now.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
All right, Kyle. Thank you.
Kyle!
But, Kyle, why didn't you rebook
your ticket?
Fine, it's your family.
All right,
just bring something home.
Nice.
Thank you, bye.
This is good now.
The connection is stable.
Right. Thanks, Peter.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Still no word from Joey?
None.
Better not contact her anymore.
It might make things worse.
[PHONE CHIMES]
Peter...
Andrew said we're starting.
[INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[INTENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Sir, the vehicle is here.
Good.
[INTENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE RINGING]
[PHONE BUZZING]
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
Berdugo, this is Delgado.
Major, is there a problem?
Your request is here.
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
It's here, Sir.
Are you sure we can trust
what you brought?
Then check it out yourself!
Release your hostages!
Easy.
We'll get there, Major.
How long will you hide
behind your hostages?
Behind your own family?
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Is that the Berdugo
everyone fears?
I really admire you, Andrew.
You and Rebecca
are exactly alike.
I admire how frank
your words are.
That's why I really want you
out of my way.
You're lucky,
you only got beaten up.
[INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [THUDDING]
- [ANDREW GROANING]
You animal!
So, you were behind that?
Well...
you're really good,
Brotherinlaw.
You fooled us for so long,
even the police.
You were like an urban legend,
disguised as Berdugo.
I'll take that as a compliment
coming from a brave journalist
like you.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Hush, calm down.
[MOUTHS]
So, tell me, Berdugo...
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
How many tons of drugs
have you sold
and how many lives have you
destroyed?
I'm just a businessman, Andrew.
Don't put all the blame on me.
I'm just the seller.
It's still up to them
if they buy or not,
if they want to be
junkies or not.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Berdugo is insane!
It's all your fault!
Madman!
Hey...
wait, wait, is this a glitch?
The live suddenly hit
100,000 views.
Look, there's so many!
What did you do?
The usual.
I contacted journalists
and influencer contacts.
Solid.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[CLICKS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[MOUTHS INDISTINCTLY]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
Isn't that poetic?
That I was the one
who gave you a medal
for being my valiant savior?
You talk too much!
Let's end this!
Joey, Jin Ho,
Berdugo is coming back.
Joey, where are you?
I need your help.
Let's go to the hangar.
The pilot is on the way,
Berdugo.
What's that? A live?
Boss, someone's chasing us.
Guys, help us.
Pass this to the police
or to Tirada Express.
Berdugo's vehicle
is right in front of me.
Tirada and Saludo viewers...
I'm not Boss Idol,
but we have only one mission...
and that is to capture Berdugo.